Jai Jinendra
Hello,
I want to give you information about an excellent product, the
meaning of being a Kamni Kamal is
Krish. It
covers 2 major and minus critical diseases, it does what it is
meant to do, it is the
best product
[Music]
Why is this policy installed
And financial support for a peaceful life and family, we will
talk about heart attack later,
it
covers a total of 92 diseases, in which there are
four diseases in major including cancer and
one disease in a month, Hot Lady is born with 10
diseases, Mahendra has 11 diseases, main
translation is 14
- 12 -
- 5 days,
this policy is available only after diagnosis,
his father gave it to people in its name, it is
just to sleep from the tent, there is no shame
[Music]
It is called removal, where it will be given to
you, it
becomes a great benefit for you because
here if any understanding person is 40 years old
and